<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Utku Yegen</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Utku Yegen</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 15:39:42 +0300</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>IconCraft AI &gt; Privacy Policies</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/iconcraftai_pp/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 15:39:42 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/projects/iconcraftai_pp/</guid>
      <description>Privacy Policy for IconCraft AI Effective Date: 03 January 2025&#xA;At IconCraft AI, your privacy is our top priority. This Privacy Policy outlines how we handle your information. By using our application, you agree to the terms described below.&#xA;Information We Collect We do not collect, store, or process any personal data from our users.&#xA;How We Use Your Information Since we do not collect any data, there is no information to use, process, or share.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IconCraft AI</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/iconcraftai/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 15:34:54 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/projects/iconcraftai/</guid>
      <description>Transform your app ideas into stunning icons and assets with IconCraft AI - your all-in-one solution for professional app icon generation and asset management.&#xA;AI-POWERED ICON GENERATION Create unique app icons from text descriptions Choose from multiple artistic styles: Engraving: Classic, detailed aesthetic Line Art: Clean, minimalist designs Line Circuit: Modern, tech-inspired look Linocut: Bold, artistic prints Preview icons instantly Generate icons optimized for all platforms Export in all required sizes automatically SMART ASSET GENERATOR Convert any image into platform-ready assets Automatically generate 1x, 2x, and 3x resolutions Export ready-to-use asset catalogs Drag-and-drop interface for easy importing Batch processing for multiple assets Export in industry-standard formats PLATFORM SUPPORT Generate icons and assets for:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GoHugo Tutorial</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/gohugo_tutor/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 22:39:21 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/gohugo_tutor/</guid>
      <description>What is GoHugo Hugo is one of the most popular open-source static site generators. With its amazing speed and flexibility, Hugo makes building websites fun again.&#xA;If you want to create a static web site like simple portfolio or landing page you can use Hugo.&#xA;Installation Official installation steps.&#xA;How did I install I just need to install hugo. Because I already have go.&#xA;brew install hugo Create your static web site line say hugo to create new site which is named quickstart.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lullabylane &gt; Terms and Conditions</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/lullabylane_tc/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 16:38:45 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/projects/lullabylane_tc/</guid>
      <description>English Terms &amp;amp; Conditions&#xA;By downloading or using the app, these terms will automatically apply to you – you should make sure therefore that you read them carefully before using the app. You’re not allowed to copy or modify the app, any part of the app, or our trademarks in any way. You’re not allowed to attempt to extract the source code of the app, and you also shouldn’t try to translate the app into other languages or make derivative versions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lullabylane &gt; Privacy Policies</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/lullabylane_pp/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 16:38:40 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/projects/lullabylane_pp/</guid>
      <description>English Privacy Policy&#xA;Utku Yeğen built the Lullaby Lane app as a Commercial app. This SERVICE is provided by Utku Yeğen and is intended for use as is.&#xA;This page is used to inform visitors regarding my policies with the collection, use, and disclosure of Personal Information if anyone decided to use my Service.&#xA;If you choose to use my Service, then you agree to the collection and use of information in relation to this policy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First Post</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/first_post/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 14:12:39 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/first_post/</guid>
      <description>Empty post for personal blog.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lullabylane</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/lullabylane/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 12:36:33 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/projects/lullabylane/</guid>
      <description>Create bedtime stories powered by AI with your child&amp;rsquo;s name, age and gender!&#xA;Bedtime stories have never been this special! With Lullaby Lane, you can create unique and personalized bedtime stories for your child by simply entering a few information. Enter the parents&amp;rsquo; names, your child&amp;rsquo;s name, age and gender, and if you wish, add a few keywords or phrases related to the plot of the story. With this information, our application will create a special story that will nourish your child&amp;rsquo;s imagination and creativity.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
